PAULOPMANN

FULLSTACKDEVELOPER

CONTACT

+372 56689 018

paul.opmann@gmail.com

paulopmann.com Estonia,

Talling

EXPERTISE

- Node.js, Next.js, Nest.js (TypeScript)
- SQL / NoSQL (MongoDB, Redis)
- AWS, Firebase, Google Cloud
- Elasticsearch, RabbitMQ
- REST / GraphQL API
- Docker
- React, React Native (TypeScript) redux,
- iotai, zuztand
- PostCSS / SCSS
- Tailwind / styled-components webpack
- php, Go, Java, python

•

EDUCATION

BoS - Computer Science 2018-present



Tallinn University of Technology



Estonia, Tallinn

Exchange Study

2022-present



Korea University



South Korea, Seoul

LANGUAGES

English Advanced

Russian Native

Estonian Upper Intermediate

Korean Elementary

ABOUT ME

Passionate problem solver with over 4 years of hands-on experience in full stack web application development, having extensive experience with TypeScript always ready to jump at any opportunity to challenge and further improve his skillset.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Full Stack Developer

Lawato (co-founder)

2022/07-present

- · Managed cloud infrastructure and optimized services to minimize costs. Designed,
- developed, and took part in the implementation of the architecture for the MVP of the SaaS.

Full Stack Developer

Lumav Commerce [remote]

11/2021-11/2022

- Optimized the performance of existing PWA applications.
- Built custom functionality modules for Magento 2 powered e-commerce applications.
- Implemented new and adjusted existing features in accordance with client requirements, software specification and design.

Full Stack Developer

Havas Estonia

Estonia, Tallinn

02/2021-06/2021

- Built and managed back-end microservices.
- Translated provided designs into UI elements.
- Engaged in the process of cross-platform mobile application development.

Full Stack Developer

Freelance [remote]

2020-present

- Consulted clients on the technical requirements and potential costs.
- Built custom page parsers for data export.
- Built custom automation scripts and browser extensions.
- Engaged in the development of software MVP as both FE and BE developer..

Back End Developer

Pipedrive

Estonia, Tallinn

08/2019-05/2020

- Built and managed back-end microservices.
- Leveraged Agile methodologies to move the development lifecycle rapidly through initial prototyping to enterprise-quality testing and final implementation. Took part in
- the on-call rotation.
- · Created and managed existing APIs.